

BRAYAN RONALDO MOJICA BARRIOS

Desarrollador Web FullStack

Contacto —

(+57) 311 236 6178



(8) 269 6764



ronaldomb98@gmail.com



ronaldomb98



ronaldo.mojica.12

Acerca de mi-

La presente es mi hoja de vida, en la cual, plasmo mi perfil académico, experiencia laboral, mis referencias personales y las competencias que considero hacen de mi perfil el indicado para desempeñarme como Desarrollador FullStack.

Intereses

Experiencia de usuario

Planeación y Diagramación

Desarrollo Front-End

Desarrollo Back-End

DATOS PERSONALES

NOMBRES : BRAYAN RONALDO
APELLIDOS : MOJICA BARRIOS
FECHA DE NACIMIENTO : MAYO 12 DE 1998
LUGAR DE NACIMIENTO : IBAGUÉ - TOLIMA

EDAD : 19 AÑOS

CÉDULA : 1.110.590.392 DE IBAGUÉ

ESTADO CIVIL : SOLTERO

DIRECCIÓN DE RESIDENCIA : SMZ 5 MZ 3 CASA 16, BARRIO TUNJOS 1

TELEFONO FIJO : 2696764 **CELULAR** : 3112366178

CORREO ELECTRÓNICO : ronaldomb98@gmail.com
NOMBRE DEL PADRE : EFREY MOJICA CANIZALES

NOMBRE DE LA MADRE : DORIS NIDYA BARRIOS HERNANDEZ

FORMACIÓN ACADÉMICA

EDUCACIÓN BÁSICA PRIMARIA

COLEGIO : JOSÉ JOAQUÍN FLOREZ HERNÁNDEZ

FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN : 25 DE NOVIEMBRE DEL 2008

EDUCACIÓN BÁSICA SECUNDARIA Y MEDIA

COLEGIO : ESCUELA NORMAL SUPERIOR DE IBAGUÉ

TITULO OBTENIDO : BACHILLER ACADÉMICO CON

PROFUNDIZACIÓN EN EDUCACIÓN

FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN : 25 DE NOVIEMBRE DEL 2008

ESTUDIOS SUPERIORES

TECNOLOGÍA

INSTITUCIÓN : UNIVERSIDAD DEL TOLIMA
TITULO OBTENIDO : TECNOLOGÍA EN GESTIÓN
DE BASES DE DATOS

: 3 DE AGOSTO DEL 2017

INGENIERÍA

INSTITUCIÓN : UNIVERSIDAD DEL TOLIMA PROGRAMA ACADÉMICO : INGENIERÍA DE SISTEMAS

ESTADO : EN CURSO

FECHA DE GRADUACIÓN

NOTA: ACTUALMENTE ESTOY CURSANDO SÉPTIMO SEMESTRE DEL PROGRAMA ACADÉMICO.



BRAYAN RONALDO MOJICA BARRIOS

Desarrollador Web FullStack

TALLERES Y CURSOS

DISEÑAR UNA APLICACIÓN WEB DE SOPORTE QR PARA DAR INFOR-2016 MACIÓN NUTRICIONAL DE LAS PRINCIPALES FRUTAS CULTIVADAS

EN IBAGUÉ Universidad del Tolima, Colombia

Expositor del proyecto en el iv foro de investigación formativa, **TALLER**

efectuado el dia sábado 31 de octubre de 2015, organizado por el programa de ingeniería de sistemas de la universidad del tolima.

DESARROLLO DE APLICACIONES WEB CON PHP 2017 SENA, Colombia

CURSO Se trabajo con el Framework Laravel

2017 **DESARROLLO DE APLICACIONES WEB**

UTILIZANDO API'S DE HTML5 SENA, Colombia

CURSO HTML5 - CSS3

OTROS

2015 - 2016 INGLÉS Universidad Del Tolima, Colombia

Cursé y Aprové 7 niveles de Ingles



BRAYAN RONALDO MOJICA BARRIOS

Desarrollador Web FullStack



(+57) 311 236 6178



(8) 269 6764



ronaldomb98@gmail.com



ronaldomb98



ronaldo.mojica.12

Skills

Overview



Programming

 $0\ LOC \longrightarrow 5000\ LOC$

HTML5 • JS • Python

Java • SQL • LATEX

C • C++ • R

Projects —

DecAR - An augmented reality interior decoration app for Android **CIS*6320** - An implementation of the Bicubic interpolation algorithm in C++ **CIS*6650** - A comparative statistical

Education

2015 - 2017 MSc., Computer Science (GPA: 3.7/4.0) University of Guelph, Canada

2009 - 2013 BEng., Computer Engineering (GPA: 4.0/4.0) University of Pune, India

Research

2015 - 2017 MSc. Candidate, Graduate Research Assistant
Thesis: Data Integration from Multiple Historical Sources to Study
Canadian Casualties of WWI

- Proposed a scalable stepwise deterministic method to reliably integrate datasets without labeled data. The method performs comparably with a method that incorporates a Support Vector Machine
- Constructed a rich longitudinal dataset to enable comphrehensive time-series analyses about WWI Canadian society and military
- Tools: R, Python, scikit-learn, BeautifulSoup, pandas, matplotlib

Publications

L. Antonie, H. Gadgil, G. Grewal, and K. Inwood, "Historical Data Integration - A Study of WWI Canadian Soldiers," in 2016 IEEE 16th International Conference on Data Mining Workshops (ICDMW), pp. 186-193, IEEE, 2016.

Experience

April 2017 - **Data Engineer** Present

Bel

 Currently involved in building a realtime data ingestion pipeline on a Kafka cluster using Spark Streaming, to detect SMS spammers on Bell's network in realtime

Sep 2015 -May 2016

Co-founder & Full Stack Developer

LocalXChange Inc.

- In a team of 2, raised \$8,000 in funding from The Hub incubator at the University of Guelph, to develop a prototype hyperlocal content platform, aimed at delivering local news and events from community organizations to local users in realtime (i.e., hyperlocal)
- In a team of 3, built hybrid mobile & web apps with Ionic, Angular.js and MongoDB, surpassing 1,000 users within a month since launch
- Met with city officials, including the Mayor of Guelph, and university officials to discuss marketing & business strategies for the platform

Sep 2015 -Dec 2016

Graduate Teaching Assistant

University of Guelph

 TA for CIS*2430 (OOP), CIS*4150 (Software Reliability & Testing) and CIS*3530 (Database Systems & Concepts) courses

Dec 2013 - **Test** Apr 2015

Test Automation Engineer

Synechron

- Developed a Keyword Driven and Behavior Driven test automation framework for Microsoft Dynamics CRM. Wrote an efficient recursive function to search multi-level frames, reducing development time by approximately two weeks. Won SPOT award

 My work opened up a new position in the organization, enabling it to earn additional revenue of \$3,500 per month (estimated)
- Demonstrated by proof of concept that rewriting a test automation framework for Microsoft Dynamics AX, using an open source library (White) instead of a proprietary one (Coded UI), would enable the team to save \$4,000 annually by downgrading the prevailing edition of Microsoft Visual Studio from *Premium* to *Professional*